Anthony D. Snelling

Service Industry Professional

1003 Summer Hill Carmel, IN 46032 (317) 702 6762 ADSnelling@comcast.net

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Quality shift management professional in the food and retail industry with experience in various restaurant environments including but not limited to: Catering, fast food, fast casual dining, as well as multiple retail stores from chain specialty retail stores to liquor retailers. Comfortable working in a substantial range of positions and fields in the service industry. Capable of learning skills in a quick and timely manner while also able to explain and describe possibly difficult processes involved in various fields. Excellent time management skills; able to properly and quickly determine the best course of action for the majority of possible situations involving the service industry. Comfortable operating in entry-level positions with the opportunity for advancement.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Excellent Customer Service Qualities
- Various POS System Experience
- Closing Paperwork and Money Management Skills
- Proficient in Microsoft Office
- Up to date with current social media platforms including but not limited to; Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram

EXPERIENCE

Payless Liquors, Southport, IN - Sales Associate

October 2016 - January 2017

- Responsible for all closing duties including but not limited to: Counting money and filing paperwork, stocking, ordering product in a timely manner
- Also responsible for knowing and operating POS systems as well as various lottery systems

Scotty's Brew Club, Franklin, IN - Cook/Catering Chef

- Responsible for planning and in turn preparing food in the allotted time provided for large catering events such as weddings and corporate business dinners
- Also responsible for managing multiple stations in the kitchen during regular business hours

Roscoe's Tacos, Southport, IN - Shift Lead

January 2015 - August 2015

- Responsible for all closing and opening duties; Paperwork, money management, as well as ensuring all sections of the restaurant were in proper working order and cleaned in a timely fashion
- Also responsible for determining which positions employees were required to work in to ensure a sufficient team capable of taking, and preparing all orders as quickly as possible without sacrificing quality food or service

Dairy Queen, Whiteland, IN - Head Cook

August 2015 - February 2016

- Responsible for managing kitchen duties and ensuring that all employees working in the kitchen were more than capable of preparing any item on the menu should they be left alone
- Also responsible for storing and organizing multiple product deliveries on a weekly basis and ensuring the product be fresh and always prepared in the correct manner

Zumiez, Lafayette, IN - Key Holder/Skate Associate

August 2013 - May 2014

- Responsible for various closing duties such as locking the doors as well as money management including the counting and preparation of nightly deposits
- Also responsible for building and selling all skateboards in the store in a timely manner while also ensuring sales for the day were above goals for all employees on shift

EDUCATION

Carmel High School, Carmel, IN - Core 40 Diploma

August 2009 - May 2013

Coursework Includes: Various culinary courses, IT and computer programming courses, including Technical Theatre and manufacturing programs